[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "name": "Test 1",
        "link": "/createdTest1",
        "state": "published",
        "preguntas": [
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "1"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "name": "Test 2",
        "link": "/createdTest2",
        "state": "not-published",
        "preguntas": [
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "1"
            },
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "2"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "name": "Test 3",
        "link": "/createdTest3",
        "state": "published",
        "preguntas": [
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "1"
            },
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "2"
            },
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "3"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "name": "Test 4",
        "link": "/createdTest4",
        "state": "not-published",
        "preguntas": [
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "1"
            },
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "2"
            },
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "3"
            },
            {
                "question" : "Is this a question example?",
                "option1" : "Yes",
                "option2" : "No",
                "option3" : "Maybe",
                "option4" : "WTF",
                "answer" : "4"
            }
        ]
    }
]